Boosting, as we saw before,
跟我们之前看的一样
is a bit more elaborate.
boosting 更加复杂
There are a few ways to do it but one of the most popular is this algorithm, AdaBoost,
有多种方法可以实现 boosting 但最普遍的一种算法是 AdaBoost（自适应增强算法）
discovered by Freund and Schapire in 1996,
是 1996 年由 Freund 和 Schapire 提出的
and here's the gist of it,
稍后我们会详细地探讨它的数学原理
although we'll develop the math in a bit more detail later.
但这个算法的要旨就是
I must say, if you look at it in the literature,
首先要说明 如果你查阅文献资料
you may find that a bit different.
文献中的表述可能会不一样
But I promise you, aside from trivial things like
但我保证 除了一些细枝末节的东西
multiplying all the weights by its constants which won't change the outcome,
例如要用所有的权重系数乘以常量 这不会改变最终结果
what I'll be showing you with the exact same Adaboost algorithm.
我将完整地介绍 AdaBoost 算法
The idea is the following: we fit our first learner in order to
我们拟合第一个学习器 以最大程度上保证准确率
maximize accuracy or equivalently minimize the number of errors.
或者最小程度上减少错误数量
There's so few good ones but one can check that we can do no better than three errors,
它的性能不是那么好 但它犯的错误数量在三个以内
so let's fit it and this is the model.
所以 我们将它拟合 得到需要的模型
We'll remember this model for later.
记住这个模型 稍后会用到
Now, our second learner needs to fix on the mistakes that this one has made.
第二个学习器需要修正第一个学习器所犯的错误
So what we'll do is we'll take the misclassified points and make them bigger.
所以我们要做的就是 筛选出那些错误分类的点 并把它们放大
In other words, we'll punish the model more if it misses these points.
换句话说 如果该模型没有筛选出这些点 我们就要惩罚它
So, the next weak learner needs to focus on these more.
让下一个弱学习器要更关注这些
Our second weak learner will be this one which correctly classifies these points.
这是第二个弱学习器 它能够正确的把这些点分类
We'll remember this form for later.
记住这个形式 稍后会用到
Now again, we punish the points that are misclassified
同样 我们要选出那些错误分类的点
by this one by enlarging these points over here.
把这些点放大
On our third weak learner is this one which tries really
这是第三个弱学习器 它要努力修正这些错误
hard to correctly classify the big points. We'll remember this one.
将这些放大的点正确分类 同样要记住这个模型
Now, we can keep going but let's say three is enough.
这个流程可能要继续下去 但我们假设三步已经足够了
Now, we want to combine these models,
现在要做的就是把这些模型集成在一起
and I'll be more specific about combining the later.
我之后会更加具体的讲解这个集成的过程
But for now, let's imagine that we're making them both like before.
但现在 我们先假设像之前一样处理
So, our resulting model is this,
这就是我们的结果模型
which when we fit in the data,
当我们用这个模型处理数据的时候
we realize it fits it very well.
发现效果非常好
So as I said, I was a bit vague on the details,
我之前也说过 细节方面不会讲解过深
but let me be more specific in the next few videos.
我在之后的视频中会进一步解释